DECEMBER 29, 2022 AINCRAD, FLOOR FOUR
Don't get too tense.
Don't treat me like a newbie!
And don't you need to get
your weapon serviced, Kirito?
Of course. I took care of that yesterday.
How about you, Asuna?
Guess I should've saved my breath!
For sure. This sword is my baby, after all.
All right, it's time. Why
don't we get started?
For those of you who don't know me, I'm
Lind from the Dragon Knights Brigade.
I'm your raid leader for this mission.
Glad to meet you all!
GUILD DRAGON KNIGHTS BRIGADE (DKB)
Huh!
I'm Kibaou of the Aincrad Liberation Squad.
I'll be your sub-leader today. Let's do this!
GUILD AINCRAD LIBERATION SQUAD (ALS)
Yeah!
About the boss's attack patterns and each
squad's role, it's just like I explained earlier.
We couldn't have gotten this far
without all you top players!
And if you can lend those
skills of yours to this leader,
I'm sure that we can defeat
this Floor Boss, too!
Leader, my eye! All you did was find
the Boss Room a second before us.
But you know those are the rules.
Don't tell me you're feeling
salty about that now?
Huh! I wouldn't say that.
Listen up! We're making
it to Floor Five today!
Yeah! You said it!
Almost there, guys! Just keep going!
Right!
Your gauges just dropped!
Squad D, get ready to switch!
Squad A, get ready to charge!
What the hell? We're not done yet!
I'm your leader! Stick to the rotation!
Sounds like an excuse to grab
the last attack for yourselves!
It's plain as day!
You can't be serious.
It's coming!
Asuna!
Kirito!
Argo!
Here we go!
Let's go, Asuna!
Right!
Would you get off me already, Kibaou?
How about getting your guys off me first?
SWORD ART ONLINE THE MOVIE
-PROGRESSIVE- SCHERZO OF DEEP NIGHT
DECEMBER 29, 2022 AINCRAD,
FLOOR FIVE, KARLUIN
All right, to celebrate
reaching Floor Five...
Cheers!
...Cheers.
Hey, miss! Hit me again!
We owe you big time for helping
us out in that Boss Raid, Argo.
Since I didn't get a chance
to put the tip about
the Boss Room possibly flooding
into my strategy guide,
that was the least I could do.
To be honest, I was sure you'd turn me down.
Needless to say, you'll
be getting my bill later!
Hey, go easy on me, okay?
Still, clearing Floor Four
took about a week, huh?
Quicker than I thought.
Considering Floor One took
a whole month to clear...
If we keep up this pace, we can reach
Floor Six before the year's out, huh?
No way, there's only two
days left in the year.
I wouldn't call that doable... Huh?
Uh, Asuna?
No way it wasn't simultaneous.
Huh? What was?
That last attack bonus!
Oh, uh... well...
That last move... our sword skills both
landed at the same time, and you know it!
R-Right.
And that gives you the right
to the bonus because...?
Uh... well, that's because...
I guess my skill must've landed just a split
second before yours. Sound about right?
Oh, no... it was simultaneous!
- But the system recognized my skill as
being first. - Thank you for your patience.
Hey, here it is!
Come on, Argo, tell her!
Don't pull me into your couple's quarrel.
- Huh? - Couple?
Anyway, Aachan.
Pass me that roast chicken
over there, will you?
S-Sure.
But you're right, we're on a blistering pace.
Huh? For what?
These raids.
Floors Two, Three, and Four.
The pace is only ramping up.
That's thanks to Kibaou's ALS and Lind's
DKB blatantly trying to one-up each other.
Which has led to good results till now,
but it's still such a flawed approach.
They weren't in synch during
yesterday's Boss Raid, either.
Well, those guys keep getting
into it every time they meet up.
The Assault Team that we have today is an
offshoot of Diabel's raid party, right?
And since Diabel was killed
in the Floor One Boss Raid,
Lind took over and created DKB, right?
But then Kibaou started chafing against
Lind's leadership-oriented methods,
and started the more teamwork-oriented ALS.